SEAN KENNEDY

SUMMARY

Highly motivated team player, whose previous work experience has sharpened multitasking and interpersonal skills. Creative, resourceful, and flexible in navigating unfamiliar situations or tasks. Effective working independently or in a group setting to accomplish goals.

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, Node.js, Javascript, React, SQLite, PostgreSQL, Webflow, Material UI, Bootstrap, LESS, SASS, Express, Cors, Knex

PROJECTS

PropertEAZY

A property management application that aims to streamline communication between owner and tenant

React | Node.js | SQLite | PostgreSQL | Material UI | Express | Helmet | Morgan | Cors | Knex

- Served as the front end developer, focusing on building the user interface and implementing third party API's
- Added a file uploading feature to organize contracts, photos for maintenance needs, or other documents between tenant and owner
- Designed a responsive website by utilizing the Material UI framework

Rides for Life

Ride application to assist pregnant Ugandan mothers with flip phones connect with a local driver for transportation during labor React | Node.js | Python| CSS | Material UI | FrontlineSMS

- Created in 6 weeks on a team of 4 developers
- Served as the front end developer, focusing on building the user interface, connecting to the back end, and styling
- Developed based on specifications outlined by a non-profit client, to address the logistics of the Safe Mothers, Safe Babies program

EMPLOYMENT

Brigham and Women's Hospital (Harvard Medical School), Front End Developer (contract), Boston, MA (Remote)

2019 - 2020

- Rebuild website to address product needs and concerns, utilizing Webflow CMS
- Provide client with detailed weekly progress reports, syncing on next steps for project

Markey's Rental and Staging, A/V Technician, Merrillville, IN

2017 - Current

- Organize and tear down audio, video, and stage equipment
- Construct physical stages based on presentation needs
- Run cameras and audio for recording speaker presentations

Northern Trust Bank, A/V Technician, Chicago, IL

2017 - 2018

- Facilitated video and audio conferences with partners of the bank all over the world
- Answered hotline calls to troubleshoot problems with partners
- Scheduled and planned meetings with partners to ensure effective communication

ESPN 3 Ball State Video Boards (On Campus Internship), A/V Technician, Muncie IN

2016 - 2017

- Facilitated both handheld and stationary cameras for televised sporting events on Ball State campus
- Organized production of setting up and tearing down all audio and visual equipment

EDUCATION

Lambda School, Remote

Full Stack Web Development and Computer Science

Ball State University, Muncie, IN

2013 - 2017

2018 - 2019

Bachelor of Arts Degree in "Telecommunications and Emerging Media"